

CONTACT ME AT

- AT POST RAJOUN BANKA BIHAR 813107
- singhbishalkumarsingh@gmail.com
- https://bishal976.github.io/
- in /bishal-kumar-054b30192/
- /bishal976/
- @BishalK56217747

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• MERN stack Developer
- •••• Graphics Designer
- •••• Tally Accounting
- •••• English Proficiency
- • • Ms Office Suite
- ••• IOT (Internet of Things)

AWARDS RECEIVED

- 4IC@GU winner
- Qualified for NASA space App Challenge (2019)
- Best Leader, St Josephs School (2014)

BISHAL KUMAR

GRAPHICS DESIGNER AND WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

A understudy guy with stretches of involvement with Technology, Design, Innovation, Management and skill in some specialized areas such as Web Design & Development, Graphics Designing, Google Actions, Alexa Skill development and rehearsing dialects like HTML5, CSS, JAVA, Python, JavaScript, etc.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphics Designer and Web Developer

MarkSports & Program Warehouse | Oct 2020 - present

• Conduct day-to-day project coordination, planning, and implementation across multiple teams (graphics/web).

Tech Head IP Coordinator

E-Cell & IIC GU | Sept 2020 - present

- Managing, conducting, hosting & marketing of events for E-Cell and IIC GU.
- Collaborating with other teams for smooth functioning.

Accounts Manager

Maa Tara Transports Jharkhand | Oct 2020 - present

 Managing the accounts books of the transporting company on day to day basis.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Galgotias University

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech), CSE | 2019-2023

- CGPA: 9.47/10
- Bachelor in Computer Science and Engg additionally Filled 3 patents and one research paper, currently

VJ INTNL SCHL LODHIPUR GORADIH RD BHAGALPUR

Senior Secondary (XII), Science (CBSE) | 2016-2018

- CGPA: 8.03
- Volunteering for Art of Living Foundation.